<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Geoff\'s Geob</string>
    <string name="app_name_title">Geoff\'s \nGeob</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Challen\'s Chontrols</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">Navigation Menu</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_forum">Forum</string>
    <string name="menu_university_mail">University Mail</string>
    <string name="menu_quiz">Quiz</string>
    <string name="menu_homework">Homework</string>
    <string name="menu_midterm">Midterm</string>
    <string name="menu_machine_project">Machine Project</string>
    <string name="menu_random_encounter">Random Encounter</string>
    <string name="menu_button">Button</string>
    <string name="menu_enter_difficulty">Enter difficulty: </string>
    <string name="menu_help">Help</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About</string>
    <string-array name="difficulty">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="quiz_names">
        <item>Course Policies and Procedures</item>
        <item>Variables and Conditionals</item>
        <item>Loops, Arrays, and Functions</item>
        <item>Strings, More Functions, and Multi-Dimensional Arrays</item>
        <item>Introduction to Objects</item>
        <item>Objects, Continued</item>
        <item>Polymorphism and References</item>
        <item>Interfaces</item>
        <item>Algorithm Analysis and Lists</item>
        <item>Trees and Recursion</item>
        <item>Sorting</item>
        <item>Internet, Exceptions, Hashing</item>
        <item>Nothing</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="midterm_names">
        <item>Imperative Programming</item>
        <item>Object-Oriented Programming</item>
        <item>meowdterm 2</item>
        <item>Nothing</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="mp_names">
        <item>Target Mode</item>
        <item>Area Mode</item>
        <item>Web APIs</item>
        <item>Refactoring and More JSON</item>
        <item>Polymorphism</item>
        <item>Final Project</item>
        <item>Nothing</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="homework_names">
        <item>Simple Conditionals</item>
        <item>Arrays</item>
        <item>Loops</item>
        <item>Functions</item>
        <item>Strings</item>
        <item>Objects</item>
        <item>Inheritance</item>
        <item>Polymorphism</item>
        <item>Interfaces</item>
        <item>Lists</item>
        <item>Binary Trees</item>
        <item>Recursion</item>
        <item>Sorting</item>
        <item>Exceptions</item>
        <item>Hashing</item>
        <item>Nothing</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="random_encounters">
        <item>You just finished reading this amazing book called Coders, and you think that adding it to the syllabus will help students gain insight into the tech world, even if it is a little more work for them. What do you do?</item>
        <item>The administration tells you that counting attendance by following along to lecture slides isn’t a good method, since students can simply follow along for their friends given their netID and password. It wants you to use i-clickers for attendance. What do you do?</item>
        <item>MP0 is out and it\'s so hard the students need therapy! You’re not professionally trained for that, but you can help them in other ways. What do you do?</item>
        <item>You see a lot of posts on the forum and on Reddit from beginner coders claiming that CS 125 is too hard, and that it isn’t beginner-friendly. What do you do?</item>
        <item>MP1 is out, and cheating levels have increased drastically. What do you do?</item>
        <item>There’s an epidemic! Well, not really, but it’s flu season and just about three fourths of the students are coughing in lecture. What do you do?</item>
        <item>MP2 is out, and it’s harder than ever! Your students are stressed out, and your TAs and CAs are beginning to agree that it’s too hard, too. What do you do?</item>
        <item>The mid-term grades are supposed to be uploaded on self-service, but the autograder is down! What do you do?</item>
        <item>You notice that the class average is far lower than those of the previous years’, and you want to try to fix it. What do you do?</item>
        <item>You noticed a fairly offensive image on the forum with your face photoshopped onto another image—let’s not go into detail. What do you do?</item>
        <item>Your underpaid and overworked TAs and CAs are done. They go on strike against CS 125 until more are hired. What do you do?</item>
        <item>Your students have reported bugs in online grading. What do you do?</item>
        <item>Due to heavy scheduling, the administration keeps trying to postpone the CS 125 fair. They tell you now that the Fall 2019 fair must be held about a week before Spring break! What do you do?</item>
        <item>It’s the end of the semester and your students are getting bored. Most of them spend lectures watching Netflix. What do you do?</item>
        <item>Your students are losing interest in lectures, and you want to keep their attention. You’re thinking about how to fix this when your cat, Xyz, jumps onto your laptop. What do you do?</item>
        <item>It’s the end of the semester and your students are getting bored. Most of them spend lectures watching Netflix. What do you do?</item>
        <item>nothing</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="encounterHeader">
        <item>Coders</item>
        <item>Attendance</item>
        <item>Extra Office Hours</item>
        <item>Course Difficulty</item>
        <item>Cheating</item>
        <item>Coughing</item>
        <item>MP Drop</item>
        <item>Mid-term Grades</item>
        <item>Extra Credit</item>
        <item>Offensive Meme</item>
        <item>Staff Strike!</item>
        <item>Bugs</item>
        <item>CS 125 Project Fair</item>
        <item>Meow</item>
        <item>Netflix</item>
        <item>Nothing</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="positiveEncounter">
        <item>Add Coders to the syllabus</item>
        <item>Vehemently disagree and continue with your method</item>
        <item>Provide extra office hours</item>
        <item>Reduce the difficulty of the course a little.</item>
        <item>Turn a blind eye; the MP is too hard, anyway</item>
        <item>Tell the students to go home and rest</item>
        <item>Provide an MP Drop</item>
        <item>Work on it devotedly, along with all your Course Developers and TAs. </item>
        <item>Add an extra credit opportunity in MP3</item>
        <item>Take it down</item>
        <item>Agree to hire more TAs and paid CAs</item>
        <item>Fix it</item>
        <item>Accept the change in date and inform your students of the delay</item>
        <item>Bring Xyz to lecture</item>
        <item>Get the administration to block Netflix on IllinoisNet</item>
        <item>nothing</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="negativeEncounter">
        <item>Don’t add Coders to the syllabus</item>
        <item>Agree to their terms and ask your students to bring i-clickers</item>
        <item>Tell the students that they’re supposed to be overwhelmed and do nothing else</item>
        <item>Increase the difficulty instead to teach them a little discipline</item>
        <item>Create a complex plagiarism checker to counter the evil cheaters</item>
        <item>Ignore it and continue with the lecture</item>
        <item>Don’t do anything</item>
        <item>Delay the mid-term grades a little and work on fixing it slowly</item>
        <item>Do nothing, remind your students that office hours exist</item>
        <item>Leave it up</item>
        <item>Drown them in legal notices until they’re forced to go back to work</item>
        <item>Don’t fix it</item>
        <item>Aggressively pursue them until you get the date you’d initially asked for</item>
        <item>Do not bring Xyz to lecture</item>
        <item>Ignore it</item>
        <item>nothing</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="encounterForumFirstNames">
        <item>nothing</item>
        <item>Whiny STEM Kid</item>
        <item>Broke College Kid</item>
        <item>Depressed Student</item>
        <item>Struggling Beginner</item>
        <item>Dishonest Prick</item>
        <item>Sick Kid</item>
        <item>Struggling Student</item>
        <item>Confused Kid</item>
        <item>Student who bombed 4 quizzes in a row</item>
        <item>Edgy kid</item>
        <item>Satisfied Student</item>
        <item>Ben Fan 3000</item>
        <item>Uninspired student</item>
        <item>Cat Lady</item>
        <item>Nothing</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="encounterForumFirst">
        <item>nothing</item>
        <item>Nooooo I hate Coders because I think I\'m a superior STEM student who should not READ and should only do STEM stuff</item>
        <item>Thank you, Geoff, for being kind enough to understand that i-clickers are an absolute waste of money. You’re my hero</item>
        <item>Oh man the extra office hours saved my life, I can finally go to bed</item>
        <item>I’m glad that Geoff hasn’t acknowledged the cheating… the course is really hard on beginners y\'know. btw someone send me the MP code pls because I think everyone should do my work for me since I can’t really think for myself and don’t even want to try</item>
        <item>Thanks a lot for letting us go home Geoff, I’m hoping for a speedy recovery and this really helps!</item>
        <item>Oh my god this really saved my grade. I think I might actually get a solid B now, if I work hard enough!</item>
        <item>There weren’t enough people in office hours today and I couldn’t submit my MP checkpoint on time because nobody was there to help me</item>
        <item>Oh man I really needed this extra credit to fix my GPA, this is a lifesaver</item>
        <item>Man Geoff is such a spoilsport, that was a funny meme. This is a violation of my freedom of speech!</item>
        <item>Yaaaay more TAs! Now maybe I’ll actually get some attention in office hours</item>
        <item>Honestly this was the best lecture in weeks, Ben made everything better just by existing</item>
        <item>LOL no way am I going to the project fair if it’s in Spring! I only signed up for the extra credit</item>
        <item>Ohmigosh an adorable cat in lecture is the best thing EVER, this is going on my snap</item>
        <item>Nothing</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="encounterForumSecondNames">
        <item>nothing</item>
        <item>Whiny STEM Kid</item>
        <item>Broke College Kid</item>
        <item>Depressed Student</item>
        <item>Struggling Beginner</item>
        <item>Innocent Kid</item>
        <item>Geoff</item>
        <item>Struggling Student</item>
        <item>Average Student</item>
        <item>Student who bombed 4 quizzes in a row</item>
        <item>Sane student</item>
        <item>Unhappy student</item>
        <item>All students</item>
        <item>Struggling Student</item>
        <item>Bored student</item>
        <item>Nothing</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="encounterForumSecond">
        <item>nothing</item>
        <item>I\'m so glad there isn\'t required reading for this course, this reinforces my faux feeling of superiority over other majors in other courses</item>
        <item>Why would you agree to this Geoff, I hate i-clickers they cost MONEY. f*** capitalism</item>
        <item>I just had ANOTHER mental breakdown in office hours. I can’t take this anymore, why wouldn’t you just listen to us :’(“</item>
        <item>Why do bad things happen to good people? I do all my work by myself why did the plagiarism checker think I cheated? This is really going to mess up my grade</item>
        <item>Well, I made everybody come to class and now I’m sick too. Class is cancelled, guys. Peace out.</item>
        <item>I cry myself to sleep every night because of the MP… I need therapy</item>
        <item>Lol who cares about mid-term grades, they don’t affect my GPA</item>
        <item>Office hours don’t help when TAs spend less than 4 minutes with you. I WANT EXTRA CREDIT</item>
        <item>\@Challen Why would you leave that up, this is a university course forum it’s completely inappropriate and it’s awful, I don’t want to look at that!!!!</item>
        <item>I can’t believe you’d do that to your loyal staff, Geoff. I mean, this is a new low. I hate you now</item>
        <item>GET. RID. OF. THE. DAMN. BUGS.</item>
        <item>Yaaaaay the fair gives us extra credit!! Now I definitely want to go</item>
        <item>Nothing happens in lecture anymore, I wish Geoff did something cool</item>
        <item>Nothing</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="mailAdmin">Administration</string>
    <string name"mailTACA">CS 125 TAs/CAs/CDs</string>
    <string name="mailBoth">Literally Everybody</string>

    <string-array name="encounterMailFirst">
        <item>nothing</item>
        <item>You added something unique to the coursework and we are pleased</item>
        <item>LECTURE SLIDES BAD WE WANT I-CLICKERS REEEEE</item>
        <item>I’m always helping out dumb kids in office hours and I’m T I R E D I wanna nap</item>
        <item>PURDON’T HAS WEED OUT INTRO COURSES AND NOW WE HAVE KINDERGARTEN LEVEL JAVA COURSES HOW COULD YOU DO THIS</item>
        <item>bruh are you encouraging cheating that’s straight up WRONG yo you gotta stop or we finna fire you</item>
        <item>bruh there were like 3 people in your lecture on Monday wtf are you doing</item>
        <item>Yeah we wanted the course to be hard but then we don’t have enough mental health resources to deal with all your kids so just let them be happy I guess</item>
        <item>Thanks for getting those grades up in time bud</item>
        <item>I’m tired and worn out and I wanna die</item>
        <item>Thank goodness you took that meme down, it was b a d</item>
        <item>Eugh you want to hire even m o r e people? We don’t want to throw so much money on an intro CS class geeeez</item>
        <item>we’re not happy with the substitution, just do your job Geoff</item>
        <item>Thanks for compromising buddy, we don’t really care about you and your students; we just wanted you to o b e y</item>
        <item>ARE YOU TRYING TO GET EVERYBODY CAT ALLERGIES I SNEEZE AT THE MERE THOUGHT OF A CAT OH MY GOD GEOFF</item>
        <item>nothing</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="encounterMailSecond">
        <item>nothing</item>
        <item>lol what's a coders</item>
        <item>thanks for adding i-clickers because we believe they’re useful even though they’re expensive trash</item>
        <item>lol it sucks for the students but at least we’ve got our work cut out for us</item>
        <item>That’s the spirit! Now it’s like a real college course and we maintain our reputation lol i’ve never taken a cs class idk how hard it’s supposed to be</item>
        <item>yeah that’s the spirit! Catch the evil cheaters and make them face consequences whooooo</item>
        <item>bruh you had to cancel lecture what the actual f dude</item>
        <item>We hate mental health and we only have one psychiatrist on campus, don’t attack us by making students have breakdowns man</item>
        <item>YOU DELAYED THE MID-TERM GRADES?!?!?!?!! HOW COULD YOU, YOU BETTER GET THEM UP ASAP</item>
        <item>lol idc nothing has changed for us</item>
        <item>WHY WOULD YOU LEAVE THAT TERRIBLE MEME UP OH MY GOD DUDE</item>
        <item>That was a LOW move. We love it!</item>
        <item>GET RID OF THE DAMN BUGS GEOFF</item>
        <item>You didn’t o b e y and you have angered the university administration gods, but you get what you want</item>
        <item>lol what's a Xyz</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="hw_advice_02">The students have been slogging on the homework daily. They really need a break. </string>
    <string name="hw_advice_36">I think it’s okay to give homework that’s a little challenging. Nothing too difficult, though… But I wouldn’t know, I’m just code.</string>
    <string name="hw_advice_79">The students seem ready to take on some real challenges in homework!</string>

    <string name="quiz_advice_02">Maybe you should give an easy quiz this time. The students are really stressing over their grades.</string>
    <string name="quiz_advice_36">The students would like their quizzes to be just right: not too hard, and not too easy.</string>
    <string name="quiz_advice_79">The students aren’t taking the quizzes seriously enough. Maybe you should remind them that they need to properly study for this course.</string>

    <string name="mp_advice_02">The MP always ends up overwhelming a student. You should probably make this checkpoint easy.</string>
    <string name="mp_advice_36">A nice, average MP would hopefully not stress out a student but also actually make them learn useful information.</string>
    <string name="mp_advice_79">The students seem ready to take on a challenging MP!</string>

    <string name="midterm_advice_02">Maybe you should make this midterm easy. The students are really stressing over it.</string>
    <string name="midterm_advice_36">You should consider making the midterm difficulty just right: not too hard, not too easy.</string>
    <string name="midterm_advice_79">Give the students a challenge this time round! Even if they mess up, at least the midterm is only worth 2% of their grade.</string>

    <string name="forum_hw_easy">The homework today was so easy lol this class is a joke</string>
    <string name="forum_hw_hard">The homework today is too hard, I wanna die aaaaaa</string>
    <string name="forum_hw_perfect">The homework today was perfect! It was so satisfying to see I got a 100% for once</string>

    <string name="forum_quiz_easy">The quiz was too easy like WTF Geoff?!?!?!!?!?!!</string>
    <string name="forum_quiz_hard">The quiz was so hard oh my god I got like a 50%</string>
    <string name="forum_quiz_perfect">The quiz was amazing; I did amazing and it felt perfect!</string>

    <string name="forum_midterm_easy">The midterm was too easy :/ I wish I’d just prof’d out of this course</string>
    <string name="forum_midterm_hard">The midterm was really hard. I cried myself to sleep because of it :(</string>
    <string name="forum_midterm_perfect">The midterm was great; I did really well!</string>

    <string name="forum_mp_easy">The MP is too easy… I dunno if I’m even learning anything in this course</string>
    <string name="forum_mp_hard">THE MP IS TOO HARD ONLY JESUS CAN SAVE ME</string>
    <string name="forum_mp_perfect">The MP was surprisingly decent this time round. Thank goodness, my grade won’t die. </string>

    <string name="first_quiz">This is the first quiz of the course! You probably should go easy on the students to get them used to quizzes</string>
    <string name="first_homework">These are the first homework problems so you should probably make it really easy :)</string>

    <string name="five_week">5 weeks</string>
    <string name="ten_week">10 weeks</string>
    <string name="fifteen_week">15 weeks</string>
    <string name="disable_bonuses">Disable Bonuses</string>
    <string name="chuchu">Chuchu</string>
    <string name="xyz">Xyz</string>
    <string name="ben_nordick">Ben Nordick</string>
    <string name="geoffrey_challen">The real Geoffrey Challen</string>
    <string name="bonuses">Bonuses</string>
    <string name="satisfaction_university">University Satisfaction: </string>
    <string name="satisfaction_student">Student Satisfaction: </string>
    <string name="already_submit_quiz">You have submitted the quiz difficulty for this week!</string>
    <string name="already_submit_mp">You have submitted the MP difficulty for this week!</string>
    <string name="already_submit_hw">You have submitted the homework difficulty for this week!</string>
    <string name="already_submit_midterm">You have submitted the midterm difficulty for this week!</string>
    <string name="no_quiz">There are no quizzes this week. Check back later!</string>
    <string name="no_mp">There is no MP this week. Check back later!</string>
    <string name="no_midterm">There are no midterms this week. Check back later!</string>
    <string name="text_submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="cat_mode">Cat mode</string>
    <string name="disable_progress_bars">Hide satisfaction meters</string>
    <string name="disable_encounters">Disable encounters</string>
    <string name="text_general">General</string>
    <string name="text_volume">Volume</string>
    <string name="half">50%</string>
    <string name="text_about">About</string>
    <string name="encounter">Encounter</string>
    <string name="no_posts">There are no posts on the forum right now!</string>
    <string name="details_about">This game was created by Ishita Rao and Kanav Bhatnagar as their final project for CS 125. They cool. Pls give them an A+, they’ll give you a singular cookie.
</string>
    <string name="end_game">Game over!</string>
    <string name="chuchuText">▼・ᴥ・▼\nWho doesn\'t love dogs? If you bring Chuchu to lecture it will surely brighten up all of your students\' days.</string>
    <string name="benText">You call upon Jesus himself, the Messiah! With his big brain energy, he influences both the students and the university to help your reputation. How he does so is a mystery that us mere mortals can only hope to comprehend.</string>
    <string name="challenText">If you really need help THAT bad, why not contact the man, the myth, the legend! As an experienced professor, he can influence the university\'s opinion of you for the better. He will give a 2 hour lecture before doing so, though.</string>
    <string name="text_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="mute_sounds">Mute all sounds</string>
    <string name="reset_game">Reset Game</string>
    <string name="bg_volume">Background Volume:</string>
    <string name="sfx_volume">SFX Volume:</string>
    <string name="help_title">Help</string>
    <string name="desc_main">Welcome, Geoff! You’re back for the Fall 2019 semester to teach CS 125.
       Your students last Spring were moderately happy with your work, congrats!
       However, that means that your new batch of students and the university have high expectations from you
       to do a great job, yet again. \n\nLet\'s get started! Choose the number of weeks in the semester: </string>
    <string name="help_intro">  This is your handy help page, informing you of the various tools that’ll
       aid you in teaching your class. Tap a subheading to get more info on it.</string>
    <string name="help_home_title">\nHome</string>
    <string name="help_home_body">
    \nThe semester is divided into 5/10/15 weeks depending on what you chose. You’ll be able to go to the next week only after planning the difficulties for homework, quiz (if any), midterm (if any), and MP checkpoint (if any). Check the forum and university email every week for helpful tips!

    \n\nYou have two satisfaction bars: student satisfaction, and university satisfaction (including administration, you, and anybody who is paid to run CS 125). Your actions in the game will affect these bars. If, at any point, either of the bars hit zero, you automatically lose the game.

    \n\nEvery week, you’ll face a random encounter, and your actions will affect student and university satisfaction. Choose wisely.

    \n\nYou have three bonuses:
    \nChuchu the dog/Xyz the cat (either one): boosts student satisfaction
    \nThe real Geoff Challen: boosts university satisfaction
    \nJava Chad Ben Nordick: boosts both student and university satisfaction by a little bit
    \nYou can use each bonus only once per game.

</string>
    <string name="help_forum_title">\nForum</string>
    <string name="help_forum_body">This is where you’ll learn what your students feel about the course so far. It can be helpful to know where you’re going wrong, or what you’re doing correctly.
</string>
    <string name="help_mail_title">\nUniversity Mail</string>
    <string name="help_mail_body">This is where you’ll periodically get email from the university, letting you know if they’re happy with what you’ve been doing. This, too, can be useful in pinpointing your errors to help you make the next week better.
</string>
    <string name="help_hqmm_title">\nHomework, Quizzes, Midterms, MP</string>
    <string name="help_hqmm_body">Here, you’ll set the difficulty of each aspect of the course for the following
        week, from 0 to 9 (0 is the easiest, 9 is the hardest). There’ll also be advice that should help you decide
        the difficulty. A few things to note:
        \n1. \tMidterms are available in weeks 4, 9, and 14. \n   Quizzes are not available during these weeks.
        \n2. \tMPs start from week 2, and won’t be available in week \t   14.</string>

    <string-array name="endgame_student_0">
        <item>Wow, you handled this really badly. Everybody: your students, staff, and the administration, hate you.
            You were forced to resign, and end up hanging yourself in a janitor’s closet at Siebel.</item>
        <item>Oh no! Your students absolutely despise you, and they all stopped coming to lecture or doing anything
            related to CS 125. Depressed, you resigned as professor and never touched a computer again.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="endgame_student_40">
        <item>The university is sick of your shenanigans.
            You are forced to resign immediately, and you end up leaving the country. You never teach again.</item>
        <item>Neither your students nor the administration was happy with your work this semester.
            You are no longer allowed to hold a teaching position at UIUC. You decide to leave and try your
            hand at teaching at a different university.</item>
        <item>The administration and staff consider your work to be average, but the students are really disappointed.
            A lot of them change their major thanks to you, and nobody wants to be a CA next semester.
            You do not get more resources from the administration, but that’s okay, since you probably won’t
            have many students to teach anymore.</item>
        <item>While the administration and your staff are moderately happy with your work, your students seriously
            dislike you. This shows in the ICES forms, and nobody wants to be a CA for CS 125 next semester.
            After a little grovelling, the university is willing to provide more resources to you, to keep the class
            running.</item>
        <item>The ICES forms are filled with intense criticism of your teaching methods. You get almost no CAs for
            the next semester, and course registration drops significantly. The university is more than willing to
            provide more resources since they’re extremely happy with your work, but was it really worth it?</item>
        <item>The administration and your staff absolutely adore you! You’re offered multiple promotions into
            administrative positions, and you take them immediately. This is just as well, because your students
            seriously dislike you, and completely trashed you on the ICES forms. You’re getting paid more,
            but was it really worth it?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="endgame_student_60">
        <item>The university is sick of your shenanigans. You are forced to resign immediately, and you end up leaving
            the country. You never teach again.</item>
        <item>Your students considered your teaching to be average, but the university was not very pleased
            with your work. You have now been assigned to take CS 100.</item>
        <item>Everybody: your students, your staff, and the administration, considers your work to be average. It was a dry semester
            with nothing amazing. The expectations of you have lowered, but nothing else has changed.</item>
        <item>Expectations from your staff and the administration haven’t changed, but your students consider your work
            to be average. Buck up, Geoff!</item>
        <item>Your students find you to be average, but you did a great job satisfying the university! You’re getting
            plenty more resources, and are generally seen as a good professor by them. Maybe you should try again
            to make your students happier, however.</item>
        <item>Your students find you to be average, the university is absolutely in love with you. You’ve been approved
            for a lot more resources next semester, to try to make your students happier. </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="endgame_student_80">
        <item>The university is sick of your shenanigans. You are forced to resign immediately, and you end up leaving
            the country. You never teach again.</item>
        <item>Your students are moderately happy with your work, but you failed at pleasing the administration.
            You were placed on probation. Do better.</item>
        <item>Expectations from your students haven’t changed, but the administration and your staff consider your
            work to be average. Buck up, Geoff!</item>
        <item>Everybody: your students, your staff, and the administration, is moderately happy with your work.
            The expectations from you haven’t changed much, and nothing much happened.
            Nothing much WILL happen, either.</item>
        <item>Expectations from your students haven’t changed, but you did a great job satisfying the administration
            and your staff. You are generally seen as a good professor, and did a better job than you did
            last semester. Congrats!</item>
        <item>The expectations from your students haven’t changed much, but the administration and your staff
            absolutely adore you. They’re inviting you to your weddings and are making Geoff-themed cakes,
            just for you. Good Geob!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="endgame_student_99">
        <item>The university is sick of your shenanigans. You are forced to resign immediately, and you end up leaving
            the country. You never teach again.</item>
        <item>Your students are extremely happy with your teaching and grading processes, congrats!
            They even send you cards on your birthday. However, you failed at pleasing the administration
            and your staff; you end up facing a lot of cuts for CS 125.</item>
        <item>Your students are extremely happy with your teaching and grading processes, congrats!
            They even send you cards on your birthday. The administration and your staff consider your work to be average.
            You did an okay job. That’s not too bad, but you could do better.</item>
        <item>Your students are extremely happy with your teaching and grading processes, congrats!
            They even send you cards on your birthday. Expectations from the administration and your staff haven’t
            changed much. You did a better job than you did last semester. Good for you, Geoff!</item>
        <item>Whoa, you’re insanely good at professoring, Mr. Professor. You were nominated for the World’s Best Geoff
            award, and most people agree that you should win. Along with this award, you win a personal dictionary
            where all Js are replaced by Gs, and all Es are replaced by ‘Eo’s. Congrats!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="endgame_student_100">
        <item>The university is sick of your shenanigans. You are forced to resign immediately, and you end up leaving
            the country. You never teach again.</item>
        <item>The university is displeased with your work, and the course faced a lot of cuts.
            Many of your TAs and Course Developers are trying to look for different jobs. However, your students
            are perfectly satisfied with your work, congrats! Years later, when you’re old and worn, you still
            receive wedding invitations from your students.</item>
        <item>The administration and your staff consider your work to be average. However, your students
            are perfectly satisfied with your work, congrats! Years later, when you’re old and worn, you still
            receive wedding invitations from your students.</item>
        <item>The administration and your staff are moderately happy with your work. While a few of your TAs are
            still going to leave, most of them are happy to stay on! Your students are perfectly satisfied
            with your work, congrats! Years later, when you’re old and worn, you still receive wedding invitations
            from your students.</item>
        <item>Whoa, you’re insanely good at professoring, Mr. Professor. You were nominated for the World’s Best
            Geoff award, and most people agree that you should win. Along with this award, you win a personal
            dictionary where all Js are replaced by Gs, and all Es are replaced by ‘Eo’s. Congrats!</item>
        <item>You beautiful professor, you. You managed to keep your students, staff, and the administration
            perfectly happy. You miraculous professor. You genius. You’re being nominated for multiple awards for
            best professor at the U of I. I don’t know how you did it, but goddamn.
            Contact the makers of this game for a cookie.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
