<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Geoff\'s Geob</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Your laptop</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">Navigation Menu</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_forum">Forum</string>
    <string name="menu_university_mail">University Mail</string>
    <string name="menu_quiz">Quiz</string>
    <string name="menu_homework">Homework</string>
    <string name="menu_midterm">Midterm</string>
    <string name="menu_machine_project">Machine Project</string>
    <string name="menu_random_encounter">Random Encounter</string>
    <string name="menu_button">Button</string>
    <string name="menu_enter_difficulty">Enter difficulty: </string>
    <string name="menu_help">Help</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About</string>
    <string-array name="difficulty">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="quiz_names">
        <item>Course Policies and Procedures</item>
        <item>Variables and Conditionals</item>
        <item>Loops, Arrays, and Functions</item>
        <item>Strings, More Functions, and Multi-Dimensional Arrays</item>
        <item>Introduction to Objects</item>
        <item>Objects, Continued</item>
        <item>Polymorphism and References</item>
        <item>Interfaces</item>
        <item>Algorithm Analysis and Lists</item>
        <item>Trees and Recursion</item>
        <item>Sorting</item>
        <item>Internet, Exceptions, Hashing</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="midterm_names">
        <item>Imperative Programming</item>
        <item>Object-Oriented Programming</item>
        <item>meowdterm 2</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="mp_names">
        <item>Target Mode</item>
        <item>Area Mode</item>
        <item>Web APIs</item>
        <item>Refactoring and More JSON</item>
        <item>Polymorphism</item>
        <item>Final Project</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="homework_names">
        <item>Simple Conditionals</item>
        <item>Arrays</item>
        <item>Loops</item>
        <item>Functions</item>
        <item>Strings</item>
        <item>Objects</item>
        <item>Inheritance</item>
        <item>Polymorphism</item>
        <item>Interfaces</item>
        <item>Lists</item>
        <item>Binary Trees</item>
        <item>Recursion</item>
        <item>Sorting</item>
        <item>Exceptions</item>
        <item>Hashing</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="satisfaction_university">University Satisfaction: </string>
    <string name="satisfaction_student">Student Satisfaction: </string>
    <string name="already_submit_quiz">You have submitted the quiz difficulty for this week!</string>
    <string name="already_submit_mp">You have submitted the MP difficulty for this week!</string>
    <string name="already_submit_hw">You have submitted the homework difficulty for this week!</string>
    <string name="already_submit_midterm">You have submitted the midterm difficulty for this week!</string>
    <string name="no_quiz">There are no quizzes this week. Check back later!</string>
    <string name="no_mp">There is no MP this week. Check back later!</string>
    <string name="no_midterm">There are no midterms this week. Check back later!</string>
    <string name="text_submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="cat_mode">Cat mode</string>
    <string name="disable_progress_bars">Hide satisfaction meters</string>
    <string name="disable_encounters">Disable encounters</string>
    <string name="text_general">General</string>
    <string name="text_volume">Volume</string>
    <string name="text_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="mute_sounds">Mute all sounds</string>
    <string name="reset_game">Reset Game</string>
    <string name="half">50%</string>
    <string name="bg_volume">Background Volume:</string>
    <string name="sfx_volume">SFX Volume:</string>
    <string name="help_title">Help</string>
    <string name="help_intro">Welcome, Geoff! You’re back for the Fall 2019 semester to teach CS 125.
       Your students last Spring were moderately happy with your work, congrats!
       However, that means that your new batch of students and the university have high expectations from you
       to do a great job, yet again. This is your handy help page, informing you of the various tools that’ll
       aid you in teaching your class. Tap the subheading to get more info on them.</string>
    <string name="help_home_title">\nHome</string>
    <string name="help_home_body">Your semester is divided into weeks. After planning the homework, quiz, midterm (if any), and MP checkpoint (if any), you’ll be able to go on to the next week using the button in the bottom right corner. While it’s recommended that you check the forum and your university email every week, it isn’t necessary for you to do so in order to go on to the next week.

       \n\nIn this course, you have two satisfaction bars: student satisfaction, and university satisfaction. You’re supposed to keep both: your students, and the university, happy.  Based on your actions while teaching this class, the progress bars will go up or down. If, at any point, either of the bars hit zero, you automatically lose the game. As long as you keep the bars above zero, you’ll be able to reach the end of the semester and complete the game.

       \n\nEvery week, you’ll face a small challenge. This involves making a decision, which may not leave everybody happy. These decisions will usually be tradeoffs; for example, fulfilling the university’s wishes may disappoint your students. You must choose wisely.

       \n\nYou have three bonuses: Chuchu the dog or Xyz the cat, Ben Nordick the students’ main homie, and the real Geoff Challen. Each of them have a special power.
       \nChuchu/Xyz boosts student satisfaction.
       \nThe real Geoff Challen boosts university satisfaction.
       \nBen Nordick, with his alpha Java powers, boosts both student and university satisfaction by a little bit.
       \nYou can use each bonus only once per game.
</string>
    <string name="help_forum_title">\nForum</string>
    <string name="help_forum_body">This is where you’ll learn what your students feel about the course so far. It can be helpful to know where you’re going wrong, or what you’re doing correctly.
</string>
    <string name="help_mail_title">\nUniversity Mail</string>
    <string name="help_mail_body">This is where you’ll periodically get email from the university, letting you know if they’re happy with what you’ve been doing. This, too, can be useful in pinpointing your errors to help you make the next week better.
</string>
    <string name="help_homework_title">\nHomework</string>
    <string name="help_homework_body">Here, you’ll set the difficulty of the homework problems for the following week, from 0 to 9 (0 is the easiest, 9 is the hardest). There’ll be helpful advice on this page letting you know if the students think the homework has been too hard or too easy, so you can set the difficulty accordingly.
</string>
    <string name="help_quiz_title">\nQuizzes</string>
    <string name="help_quiz_body">Here, you’ll set the difficulty of the quiz for the following week, from 0 to 9 (0 is the easiest, 9 is the hardest). There’ll be helpful advice on this page letting you know if the students think the midterms/quizzes have been too hard or too easy, so you can set the difficulty accordingly.
</string>
    <string name="help_midterms_title">\nMidterms</string>
    <string name="help_midterms_body">Midterms are held every five weeks, so this section will only be available in weeks 5, 10, and 15.
Here, you’ll set the difficulty of the midterm for the following week, from 0 to 9 (0 is the easiest, 9 is the hardest). There’ll be helpful advice on this page letting you know if the students think the midterms/quizzes have been too hard or too easy, so you can set the difficulty accordingly.
</string>
    <string name="help_mp_title">\nMachine Project</string>
    <string name="help_mp_body">MP checkpoints are added every two weeks, so this section will only be available every other week. MPs won’t be available in the first two weeks of the semester. If you’ve chosen the 15 week semester setting, there won’t be an MP checkpoint in the last week, either.
Here, you’ll set the difficulty of the MP for the following week, from 0 to 9 (0 is the easiest, 9 is the hardest). There’ll be helpful advice on this page letting you know if the students think the MPs have been too hard or too easy, so you can set the difficulty accordingly.
</string>


</resources>
